stlmag.com 2013-04-29

# Privacy Policy - St. Louis, Missouri

St. Louis Magazine's privacy statement has been created to protect your privacy. We are committed to keep all customers' information confidential and secure. This policy administers the manner in which St. Louis Magazine uses and maintains information collected from its customers.

### Information we collect

St. Louis Magazine collects personal information when you register with St. Louis Magazine.com or when you order products or services. St. Louis Magazine will collect and keep information, such as:

    * Your name  
    * E-mail address  
    * Postal Address  
    * Telephone numbers  
    * Credit card information  
    * IP addresses 

### How secure is the information we collect?

At St. Louis Magazine we are extremely serious about security in order to protect your confidential information. St. Louis Magazine uses Secure Socket Layers (SSL) encryption when transmitting data on St. Louis Magazine.com. During all transactions, an icon resembling a padlock is displayed on the bottom of most browsers during SSL transactions. All financial information is encrypted, and our company databases are accessible only to internal employees.

### Cookies

What is a cookie? A cookie is a piece of information sent by a Web server to a user's browser. (A Web server is the computer that "hosts" a Web site, and responds to requests from a user's browser.) Cookies may include information such as login or registration identification, user preferences, online "shopping cart" information, etc. The browser saves the information, and sends it back to the Web server whenever the browser returns to the Web site. St. Louis Magazine uses cookies to keep track of user's preferences while the user is visiting the website. Cookies also help minimize load times and save on server processing. St. Louis Magazine may use cookies that store your information such as your password being remember or not and other information.

### Sharing and Disclosure

Occasionally St. Louis Magazine may send our customers information about our company and get in touch with you when necessary. St. Louis Magazine will not otherwise disclose its customer's personal information and account information unless St. Louis Magazine has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of St. Louis Magazine, St. Louis Magazine's customers or others. St. Louis Magazine will never disclose personal information to third parties.

### Customer Responsibilities

You are responsible for the security of your login and passwords. Make sure you keep them in a safe place and do not share them with others. Always remember to logout after your session ends to ensure that other people cannot access your account information.

###   
Changes to Privacy Policy

St. Louis Magazine may update this policy statement. We will notify you about changes by sending you a notice to the primary email address specified in your St. Louis Magazine account.
